HASSAN ALI

Teacher and Programmer

Seeking challenging opportunity and an environment to explore and fine tune my creative talent by learning new things and contributing the best of skills and abilities with having approximately 4 years of experience equipped with records of success in academic and professional grounds.



hassanali202456@gmail.com

03204148563

Lahore, Pakistan 👂

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tutor

Personal Place

01/2018 - Present

Lahore

I started my career as a tutor at my personal place where I geared up my students to learn and perform very well in their studies.

Tasks

- Teaching Science subjects to Matric students.
- Sharing Monthly reports with Guardians of my students.

School Teacher

The Royal Cambridge School System

02/2020 - Present

Lahore

I have been working with a well reputed school of Lahore with over 10 years of excellence.

Tasks

- Teaching Science subjects to Matric Students.
- Administrative Responsibilities.
- Composing all the documents, notices and exam papers for the school.

Contact: Principal - mail: trcssofficial@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Matric

The Royal Cambridge School System

02/2015 - 03/2017

Courses

Mathematics

Physics

Chemistry

Biology

ICS

The Superior group of Colleges

04/2017 - 03/2019

Courses

Mathematics

Physics

Computer Science

RSCS

PUCIT-Punjab University Lahore

10/2019 - Present

Courses

Computer Science

Programming

SKILLS

Teaching science subjects efficiently

Professional Email Writing

MS Word

MS Excel

MS Powerpoint

Coding in C

Coding in C++

Teamwork

Communication

Basic Skills of Computer

CERTIFICATES

Programming for everybody (04/2020 - 04/2020) *University of Michigan*

Python Data Structures (04/2020 - 04/2020) University of Michigan

Introduction to Data Science with Python (05/2020 - 05/2020)

University of Michigan

C for Everyone, Programming Fundamentals (06/2020 - 06/2020)

University of California, Santa Cruz

Writing Professional Emails in English (07/2020 - 07/2020)

Georgia Institute of Technology

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Punjabi

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding

Teaching

Islamic Education

Debating